[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be teachers?", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "89", "36"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is a giraffes gestation period?", "correct_answer": "14- 15 months", "incorrect_answers": ["18 - 20 months", "10 months", "9 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The breast milk of a meat-eating mother can be this much more contaminated with pesticides, compared to the milk of a vegetarian mother.", "correct_answer": "35 times", "incorrect_answers": ["25 times", "5 times", "2 times"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character does Luke call for first when hanging below Cloud City in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": "Ben Kenobi", "incorrect_answers": ["C3P0", "Yoda", "Leia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actors playing Terry Malloy and Edie Doyle in this movie won Best Actor and Best Supporting actress Oscars.", "correct_answer": "On the Waterfront", "incorrect_answers": ["My Fair Lady", "A Man for All Seasons", "The Greatest Show on Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is an example of a spoonerism?", "correct_answer": "It is kisstomery to cuss the bride.", "incorrect_answers": ["Round and round the ragged rock the ragged rascal ran.", "Able was I ere I saw Elba.", "He is at  the pineapple of his career."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie On Her Majestys Secret Service, James Bond poses as which member of the College of Arms, a genealogical society?", "correct_answer": "Sir Hilary Bray", "incorrect_answers": ["Sir Hilary  Sampson", "Sir Hilary  Lomax", "Sir Hilary Pearce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is Baby from the 1938 comedy movie Bringing Up Baby?", "correct_answer": "Leopard", "incorrect_answers": ["Elephant", "Polar bear", "Deer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals were the Canary Islands named after ?", "correct_answer": "Dogs", "incorrect_answers": ["Lions", "Cats", "Canaries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1928, the International Astronomical Union divided the sky into how many official constellations?", "correct_answer": "88", "incorrect_answers": ["77", "99", "55"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In medical terms, what is a CVA?", "correct_answer": "A stroke", "incorrect_answers": ["An aneurysm", "A type of accountant", "A heart attack"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the movie Whats Love Got To Do With It released?", "correct_answer": "1993", "incorrect_answers": ["1996", "1995", "1990"]}]